Hello hello friends how are you all Africa
Shwetark in this video today
we will tell you how to make a
credit card online if you can also get a kidney
then you can make it online
you do not need to go to the bank or any agent
so friends first of all
you will get a
link in the description box and if you make an inquiry then
this website will open in front of you
ICICI freight corridor it is
not going to cost you any money here and
neither you need to give money to anyone to
make a credit card so
what you have to do before that to
make a credit card click here you have to
click on this link as you
do this last one where your application for sacred
is going to be done the website will open in front of you
ICICI bank platinum cheap
rate card UK contact lens
technology in this you are going to get wifi
polytechnic back points
344 one setting gift voucher fuel
surcharge foolproof pause is going to come and up to life
time free minutes here it is
not going to cost you any money special
online offer if you buy this  If you apply from here,
you will get
15% cash back on Amazon and balance on Amazon up to
1500 and now up to 600 volume
maximum. You are going to get this sponge number
on Amazon if you apply cut from here. So
friends, let's start
how we do it. First of all, you have to go
here, then in the field limited will be
broken and ICC Bank credit card
limiting. First of all, you have to enter
your job city, you have to fit it here. After doing the city, you have to
enter about it. What is your friend's address and your date of
birth, you have to enter it here.
After that, you have to enter your
salary. If you are self-employed or a businessman, or
you work, then you have to
enter it here. And you have to enter your monthly salary
here too, which will be the
reality. Enter it there only. When asked about it, the
salary mode will tell you how your
salary comes in your account. You get gas, you get sex, then you have to
give the cash in the account. After that, you have to enter your PAN
card number because I
also have to do it.  You don't have to reply, I am
just telling you, after that according to the
relationship, if you have any
relation with this event, then you have to
select it here, if you do
n't have any relation, then you have to enter
your name,
your email ID,
after that you have to enter your mobile
number, you will have to
verify the mobile number,
you will also have to enter the number which you have, if you have been
robbed, robbed, then
you have to enter the company, now in which company do you work, then
you have to enter the name, if the company
name is ,
or west and if you enter the companies, then it
is okay, otherwise now leave it like this, by
clicking on agree, you have to read the terms and conditions
carefully, in this you have to take the trust, then
you have to click on cement, as soon as
you click, then here
you will see congratulations your all
eligible for an NICIC Bank
credit card, your response will be easy, get in
touch with recovery, there will be a table for the card
and soon the bank employees will
contact you and  Whatever your kidney is, we will do it.
So friends,
by following this small process, you
can easily get your ICC Bank credit card
without any charge. You are not paying any money to anyone
and you have to
use it later on as per your bank's trust. So friends, if
you liked this video, then do like, share
and subscribe. Thank you friends.